== Official || kisskh.club - kissasia.co || Thank for Support  ==
Characters, actions, places, occupations,
and events in this series
are fictional and created
for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Hey.
If you’re going to do that,
can you do it somewhere else?
The upper floors are a hotel.
It has rooms available.
Who are you?
This is none of your business.
I own this place.
If you don’t want to spend the night
at the hotel,
do you want to spend time in jail instead?
Let’s go.
This is ruining my mood.
You should leave.
I’ll see you later.
What? Are you serious?
Yes.
I don’t want to go with you anymore.
Damn it.
Why did you get in the car?
I want to be your sugar baby.
I want you to adore me.
I’m good at pampering.
Please take me.
What the hell are you saying?
What are you doing?
The other night.
When the light went off,
you stopped talking.
I thought…
you may prefer it when it’s dark.
You still haven’t told me
why you got the moon tattoo.
Why are you crying?
2 DAYS AGO.
The renovation on the 11th floor
started today, right?
Yes, Miss Chan.
The construction will be completed
within seven days.
Remind our staff
that the entire floor is closed.
I don’t want guests to stay on the floor
while the construction is ongoing.
Do not cause any noise after 6 p.m.
because it’s time for our guests to rest.
Yes, Miss Chan.
First impressions are important.
Your name tag is also important.
Yes, Miss Chan.
I’m sorry.
Miss Chan,
Miss Sun is waiting in your office.
Sun.
Hello, sister.
Why are you here to see me?
I have to attend a gala party tonight.
But I don’t want to go.
I’ve been filming for three days straight.
I’m exhausted.
So what?
Can you go to the party as me?
Let’s switch for one day.
Just like we did in high school.
You performed on stage as me.
I agreed to do that because you were sick.
That was why I sang on stage.
Speaking of singing,
are you not interested in being a singer?
When you were young,
you said you wanted to be a singer,
and I would be an actress.
No.
I like doing business now.
This is why you are Mom’s favorite.
You do everything
that she wants you to do.
So this is all you want to say to me?
Actually, I want you
to go to the party with me.
Can you go with me?
I already booked a seat for you.
You know I don’t like answering the press.
But there will be a lot of pretty girls there.
Sun.
You are so stubborn.
Fine, I’m leaving.
See you.
Bye.
I’LL TAKE YOU TO EAT DELICIOUS FOOD.
Don’t forget to wake up to eat.
Don’t sleep all day.
I’m leaving.
I’ll have an iced matcha as usual.
Thank you.
It’s so good.
So refreshing.
Do you have anything to say to me?
You are cute.
Are you hitting on me?
It’s just a compliment.
Thank you.
You are cute too.
I know.
Otherwise, you wouldn’t smile at me.
I smiled because I’ve never seen anyone
get that excited about food.
It tastes really good.
Do you want to taste it?
I’ll ask for a new straw.
No, it’s okay.
How is it?
Believe me now?
Before work,
I always eat something delicious.
I’m a regular customer here.
Their drinks and food are great.
I think I’ll become
a regular customer here too.
Then I hope we will
run into each other often.
What’s your name?
I’ll tell you
when we become acquaintances.
I hope we will become acquaintances.
Do you want another sip?
No, thanks.
I won’t bother you anymore.
Can I have a menu, please?
When you play the intro,
I’ll send you a signal, then you’ll start.
Then the rest of you follow.
Hello, Miss Chan.
Hello, we are The Petal.
This is our first day
performing at the Crescent.
I hope you will enjoy our music.
♪ It’s late at night,
have you got a ride? ♪
♪ If you haven’t, here is my invite ♪
♪ Wanna lock eyes a little longer ♪
♪ Can’t let you slip away farther ♪
♪ Can we please
spend more time together? ♪
♪ The atmosphere’s just right ♪
♪ That we’re here tonight ♪
♪ It may be because
I’m talking to you, to you ♪
♪ Last two, won’t say goodbye ♪
♪ Together, just you and I ♪
♪ It may be because
we feel the same, the same ♪
♪ Even though it’s time to part ♪
♪ Still don’t want to be apart ♪
♪ It’s late at night,
have you got a ride? ♪
♪ If you haven’t, here is my invite ♪
♪ Wanna lock eyes a little longer ♪
♪ Can’t let you slip away farther ♪
♪ Can we please
spend more time together? ♪
♪ Wanna lock eyes a little longer ♪
♪ Can’t let you slip away farther ♪
♪ Can we please
spend more time together? ♪
I MISS YOU.
CAN YOU GIVE ME ANOTHER CHANCE?
I REALLY WANT TO SEE YOU.
Excuse me.
Are you Sun?
No, I’m her big sister.
So you are Chan, her twin sister?
Yes.
This is my first time
meeting twins who are both beautiful.
But I think you look
prettier than your sister.
I’m sorry.
I don’t like men.
I like women.
You are sitting here alone.
Don’t you feel lonely?
Why don’t we drink together?
Have you been waiting long, honey?
Do you have something to say
to my girlfriend?
No.
Are you okay?
I’m okay. Thank you.
Then…
Can you buy me a glass of wine in return?
Can I have a glass of wine?
I’m Key.
This is my first day working here.
Nice to meet you.
You’re a great singer.
Thank you.
Your tattoo.
It’s pretty.
I knew you would like it.
I really like it.
Why did you get the moon tattoo?
Is there a particular reason?
If you want to know,
you need to come with me.
You are quite flirty.
Do you use that line a lot?
I only use it with you, Chan.
If I go with you,
what will I get?
I can give you everything
that makes you happy.
Fine.
But only for tonight.
We’ll be together just tonight.
What if you are addicted to me?
Are you that good?
I like your lipstick.
It makes me want to kiss you.
You want to kiss me?
Then do it.
Do you dare do it?
Why are you so rushed?
What else are you waiting for?
Can you put your hand down?
Try to relax.
Be confident and send the energy to me.
Be more confident.
Relax.
This brand is about confidence.
Show it.
Let’s take a break.
Peach.
What’s wrong?
Can we change the model?
What?
I don’t think she’s the right model
to represent the brand.
The concept of this brand is
clothes that give you confidence.
The model has no confidence.
We won’t get a good result from her.
The brand specifically chose her.
The model personally knows the company.
If you insist on having her,
I can’t continue to work.
I’ll send you the contact info
of other photographers.
Calm down, Peach.
The brand specifically asked for you.
How about this?
I’ll talk to the model.
Peach.
Key.
When did you get here?
I got here
when you were rebuking your client.
You were scary.
You don’t need to be scared.
I’m always gentle with you.
Why are you so tough with your client?
Aren’t you afraid of losing them?
No.
I’m not doing this for money.
It’s just a hobby.
A hobby?
But you are the go-to photographer
of the top actress.
You mean Sun?
We’ve been working together so often
that we’re practically friends.
Do you know her twin sister?
I met her a few times.
But I don’t know her personally.
I just want to know
if she’s seeing someone.
Has she dated anyone before?
I don’t know.
She is hard to approach.
She is very private.
She is totally different from Sun.
Why are you asking about her?
I’m just curious.
I think she’s pretty.
Key.
This Friday.
Big Mom wants to hold
a birthday celebration for Dad.
Do you want to go home?
They really miss you.
They want you to visit them.
If I don’t have a work schedule, I’ll go.
Fine.
Let me know if you’re coming.
Chan, don’t you think
the quotation is too high?
I’m just renting space
to open an Omakase restaurant.
I’m not renting the entire floor.
You know what kind of hotel
the Crescent is.
We always have VIP guests.
The price I offer you is reasonable.
I want the quotation for your friend,
not for business partners.
When it comes to business,
I don’t consider anyone my friend.
My friend is so ruthless.
Why don’t you draft a contract?
And we will discuss it again later.
Many people want to open
a restaurant in my hotel.
If you don’t hurry…
Fine. I got it.
Then do as we’ve agreed on.
Deal.
Our college classmates are holding
a reunion party early next month.
Do you want to go with me?
You haven’t seen our friends
from the US for a while.
No.
Come on. Let’s go together.
I said no.
Stop pestering me.
Simba.
How are you doing?
Are you lonely?
Are you still mad at me?
I didn’t come home just one night.
He is so mad at me.
It was just one night.
Here is your water.
Why are you so pretty?
Your eyes,
your nose,
and your lips.
I’m sorry.
Does it hurt?
No.
I want to know you more.
Don’t.
What happens between us
is for tonight only.
Won’t you see me again?
No.
What if we run into each other?
It won’t happen.
Do you know the idiom
‘once in a blue moon’?
It means rarely.
A blue moon doesn’t happen often.
But it doesn’t mean it’s impossible.
What are you trying to say?
I’m just saying…
if we run into each other again,
it may be because
we are somehow connected.
It has nothing to do with it.
What if we run into each other again?
Will you give me a chance?
Sure.
If we run into each other,
I may give you a chance.
I guess she really forgot me.
Once in a blue moon?
Silly kid.
She was talking nonsense.
Hey.
We meet again.
Have a seat.
Did you just get here,
or have you already finished your meal?
Are you here alone?
You can sit with me.
I finished my meal.
I’m about to leave.
I think we will run into each other often.
You don’t seem to enjoy your meal.
The dish is delicious.
I just feel a bit down.
So I don’t want to eat it.
Is something bothering you?
I met someone.
Don’t tell me
a pretty girl like you…
is also going through a breakup?
I can’t even call it a breakup.
It’s just a one-night stand.
Then you don’t need to care about it.
There are many girls out there.
But she…
She is different from other girls.
So this one night,
it must be really good.
Okay.
Now I get why you feel down.
I don’t want to end just one night.
Theoretically,
if you think it was a great night,
she probably feels the same.
If you were me,
what would you do?
If I were you,
I would…
make a move on her.
If she was that tasty,
I couldn’t let it end
after just one night.
Am I right?
Yes.
Good idea.
We’ve been talking for a while.
I still don’t know your name.
What’s your name?
Does it matter?
What if we run into each other often?
Don’t we need to know
each other’s names?
This way our relationship will be unique.
Good.
It’s fun. I like it.
Okay, deal.
We had a good talk today.
I hope to see you again.
Do you want to go grab a drink with me?
Sorry.
I already have a plan.
I’m meeting with my family.
Good night.
Bye.
Do you want anything else?
I have another one of these.
Hello, Miss Chan.
Is everything alright?
Yes.
Do you want your usual?
We meet again.
You.
What are you doing here?
I work here.
I work here as a singer.
That’s right.
I told you.
We would meet again.
Because I work at your bar.
Why aren’t you working today?
Today is my day off.
But actually, I want to have a side job.
Do you have another job for me?
Especially a job
where I can be close to you.
People who work closely with me
must be good at their job.
Exceptionally good.
Wasn’t I good the other night?
What are you talking about?
So naughty.
Chan.
Is this your new friend?
She’s just a silly kid.
Don’t pay attention to her.
I upset the pretty sis.
Are you here alone?
Yes.
Your cocktail looks tasty.
What is the name?
You mean the name of the cocktail?
Or my name?
Both.
But I want to know your name more.
Do you want to taste it?
It tastes good.
It tastes good. That should be enough.
You don’t need to know the name.
You are so pretty.
Do you really not have a girlfriend?
I don’t like commitment.
Me too.
Hey.
If you’re going to do that,
can you do it somewhere else?
The upper floors are a hotel.
It has rooms available.
Let’s go.
You should leave.
I’ll see you later.
What? Are you serious?
Yes.
I don’t want to go with you anymore.
Damn it.
Why did you get in the car?
I have an offer for you, pretty sis.
What is it?
I want to be your sugar baby.
I want you to adore me.
I’m good at pampering.
Please take me.
What the hell are you saying?
What are you doing?
The other night.
When the light went off,
you stopped talking.
I thought…
you may prefer it when it’s dark.
You still haven’t told me
why you got the moon tattoo.
Why are you crying?
I think…
I should go.
I’ll see you.
I’m sorry.
I shouldn't have come back.
Aunt Niam.
Good morning, Miss.
I brought a lot of delicious food for you.
Let me help you.
Yes, take this.
Let me take off my shoes first.
Did Dad and Big Mom tell you
to bring it to me?
No one told me to do this.
I made your favorite food.
So I want to give it to you.
Next time, you can have
someone deliver it to me.
How can I do that?
I made the food.
I need to deliver it myself.
Do as you please.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
I’ll put it in the refrigerator.
Simba.
Come here.
Say hi to Aunt Niam.
Look.
Aunt Niam, you’re doing it again.
I hire a helper
to clean my condo every week.
I can’t help it.
This is your condo.
I have to…
…clean it yourself.
Yes, Miss.
I almost forgot.
Madam bought cat treats for Simba.
They are in the brown bag.
I almost forgot it.
Thank you.
Alright.
She must really miss Simba.
Simba is such a cuddly cat.
Who would not fall for it?
How is she doing?
Madam?
She is losing her appetite.
She barely eats.
She also gets sick often.
Dad is probably busy with the farm, right?
Miss Key.
Can’t you find time to visit her?
Although she’s not your biological mom,
she loves you as if you were her daughter.
I can’t go back to that house.
No. Don’t think that.
It happened a long time ago.
It was not your fault.
It was my fault.
It was surely my fault.
Stop blaming yourself.
(Why are you crying?)
Shit.
Chan.
I’m sorry.
I’ll call the insurance company.
It’s okay. It’s just a small scratch.
No.
Let’s call the insurance company.
I hit your car.
I need to take responsibility.
After talking to the insurance,
I’ll buy you lunch.
Did you intentionally hit my car?
No way.
Why would I do that?
What are you doing here?
I have a practice with my band.
I didn’t mean to hit your car.
Really?
You always try to get my attention.
That’s true.
I admit it.
I want you to pay attention to me.
But not like this.
You should go.
You don’t need
to take responsibility for it.
Wait.
Since we ran into each other,
why don’t you let me buy you lunch?
As an apology.
No, I don’t need anyone to buy me lunch.
Then can you buy me lunch?
Please.
Aren’t you going to eat that?
Yes.
But it would be nice
if I could have something else too.
All you think of is that?
All I think of…
…is you
Can you be serious?
I’ll be serious.
So…
did you think about my offer?
Are you interested in having me
as your sugar baby?
Are you sure you’re being serious?
I’m absolutely serious about it.
So?
Are you interested?
I’m a businesswoman.
I don’t make a deal
that doesn’t benefit me.
Then what do you want?
I can give you everything.
I’d do anything for you.
I’ll give in to you in everything.
Just tell me.
A player like you,
how many times
have you made this kind of offer?
You are the first…
and only one.
Really?
What about your other girls?
You seem to have many girls around you.
Don’t worry.
If you take me, I’ll cut them off.
I’ll leave everything behind.
You will have all of me.
And I will have only you.
Why do I have to do that?
I can spend money
on something more useful.
Because we are a good match.
That night,
I fell for you.
You seem to be pretty into me too.
You haven’t told me
why you got the moon tattoo.
How about this?
After finishing lunch, you go to my condo.
I’ll tell you everything.
Tell me now.
I have a cat at home.
Don’t you want to see him?
He’s very cute.
You can hold him, rub his belly,
and even kiss him.
Come in.
Here are the slippers.
Simba.
You can hold him.
He won’t bite or scratch you.
He’s nice just like his owner.
It’s okay.
I’ve never held a cat before.
I don’t know how to do it.
If you are afraid, you can just pat him.
Look, who is this?
Like this.
See?
He’s cute.
I never thought I would be patting a cat.
You already fell for him.
I guess so.
You are cuddling her.
You don’t seem to have a money problem.
Why do you want to be my sugar baby?
I don’t have any money problems.
I just want to be your girl.
Stop being cryptic.
What exactly do you want from me?
Everything is related to this tattoo.
Who are you?
What did Key say, Niam?
Well…
I failed.
She refuses to come home.
Even though she knows you’re sick.
It’s not about that.
I think she still can’t forgive herself about Pin.
This will haunt our family forever.
I feel sorry for Key
for what she’s going through.
Kiran Mahattanakit.
Your last name is Mahattanakit,
but you work as a singer at my bar?
I want to be close…
to the person who saved my life.
The person who is my first love.
Hold on.
Have we met before?
I won’t tell you if we have met.
You have to remember it yourself.
But I can tell you this.
I chose to get the moon tattoo
because of you.
You are my first love.
As long as I can be with you,
it doesn’t matter what I am to you.
I’ll accept it.
Why do you want to be my sugar baby?
It seems fun.
So she and you are not
just a one-night stand anymore.
I have a new rule.
The two of us will not kiss.
What song is this?
It’s a song that I wrote.
It sounds great.
Sing it again.
You don’t need to pretend, Jay.
I know you hate me.
I just want to take what is mine back.
You have no right to touch my stuff,
especially this piano.
Hi.
Do you miss me?